[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What title was initially considered for the Greys Anatomy TV series?", "correct_answer": "Complications", "incorrect_answers": ["Shes Meredith", "Flesh And Bones", "The Human Heart"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which island is NOT a part of Greece?", "correct_answer": "Gozo", "incorrect_answers": ["Kea", "Hydra", "Kos"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Aspiration is one of the Lacoste perfumes for women.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many times did Robert Altman get married?", "correct_answer": "3", "incorrect_answers": ["2", "1", "4"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The flag of which US state features a white American Bison on a blue field?", "correct_answer": "Wyoming", "incorrect_answers": ["Nevada", "Texas", "South Dakota"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This line was spoken by actress Clara Blandick in which 1939 motion picture: Now you go feed those hogs before they worry themselves into anemia.?", "correct_answer": "The Wizard of Oz", "incorrect_answers": ["State Fair", "Oklahoma", "Gone With the Wind"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Fictional boxer Rocky and his son, Robert Jr. have a very close relationship, and in fact, Jr. followed in dads footsteps to become a professional boxer.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which collective noun denotes a group of storks?", "correct_answer": "a mustering", "incorrect_answers": ["a rafter", "a smack", "a flight"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does the expression to wear a green hat mean in popular Chinese culture?", "correct_answer": "to be a cuckold", "incorrect_answers": ["to be a peasant", "to be a wise person", "to be an immature, foolish person"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following flags doesnt include a cross?", "correct_answer": "the flag of Alaska", "incorrect_answers": ["the flag of Mississippi", "the flag of the UK", "the flag of Denmark"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which US President was nicknamed Young Hickory?", "correct_answer": "Polk", "incorrect_answers": ["Jackson", "Taylor", "Martin Van Buren"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The ghost of the 16th President of the United States Abraham Lincoln is reported to be one of the ghosts that haunt the White House.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]